biggerbids.com 2010-05-14

# BiggerBids.com - Privacy Policy

## BiggerBids.com Privacy Policy

**WHAT PERSONAL INFORMATION DOES BIGGERBIDS COLLECT AND WHY?**

To provide you with the best service possible a Seller, we collect some or all of the following information: 

  * your name 
  * e-mail address 

When you use BiggerBids's services we track your activity on our website. Your personal information is used to identify you in our system. We also track your Internet Protocol (IP) address, domain name (if applicable), browser type, and request.cookies duration. BiggerBids uses this information to administer the site and to further improve our service to you. 

Members may periodically receive e-mails from us updating you of significant events taking place at BiggerBids.

**HOW DOES BIGGERBIDS USE YOUR INFORMATION?**

BiggerBids uses your information to research usage patterns based on the information provided to us during registration, and from our server log files. We do this to better understand your needs and enhance our service to you. 

**WITH WHOM DOES BIGGERBIDS SHARE YOUR INFORMATION?**

We do not share your information with any party outside of the Nucite Solutions company. 

Please note that BiggerBids has links to other web sites. When you click on one of these links, you leave BiggerBids and go to another web site. We encourage you to read the privacy statements of these sites, to which we link, as their privacy policy may differ from ours. 

**WHAT ARE "COOKIES" AND HOW ARE THEY USED?**

A "cookie" is a small amount of data sent to your browser from a web server and stored on your computer's hard drive. Your browser must allow cookies in order for you to use the BiggerBids service. We use cookies to hold information, such as a login ID, so you don't need to re-enter information each time you utilize a BiggerBids service during a request.cookies. We also use cookies to provide customized and personalized services to you. Should you choose to set your browser to reject cookies, you will render it nearly impossible to use sites that set and use cookies, including BiggerBids. 

**HOW CAN I REVIEW AND CHANGE MY INFORMATION AND CANCEL MY BIGGERBIDS ACCOUNT?**

You can edit and change your information in your BiggerBids account, including your password and email address, at any time in the "My Account " section of the BiggerBids website. Should you forget your password, BiggerBids can send it to you immediately via e-mail, at your request. To cancel your account, please send an email to "support (at) BiggerBids (dot) com" . 

**HOW I WILL KNOW ABOUT CHANGES TO BIGGERBIDS' PRIVACY POLICY**

If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on the "Home Page" of our site so that our users are always aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under circumstances, if any, we disclose it. If at any point we decide to use personally identifiable information in a manner different from that stated at the time it was collected, we shall notify users by way of this posting. Users will have a choice as to whether or not we use their information in this different manner. We will use information in accordance with the privacy policy under which the information was collected. 

**QUESTIONS OR CONCERNS**

If you have questions or concerns regarding BiggerBids's privacy policy, kindly contact BiggerBids by e-mail at "support (at) BiggerBids (dot) com".
